export const data = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Why did the British throw tea into the Boston Harbor?",
        option1: "To protest the Tea Act",
        option2: "Because they hated tea",
        option3: "Because they were bored",
        option4: "Because they wanted to make the French mad",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "Who was the primary author of the Declaration of Independence?",
        option1: "Abraham Lincoln",
        option2: "George Washington",
        option3: "Thomas Jefferson",
        option4: "Ben Franklin",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What was the name of the first U.S. president?",
        option4: "George Washington",
        option2: "John Adams",
        option3: "Thomas Jefferson",
        option1: "James Madison",
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What was the first permanent English colony in America",
        option3: "Jamestown",
        option2: "Massacheusetts",
        option1: "New York",
        option4: "New Jersey",
        ans: 3
    },
{
        id: 5,
        question: "Which year did the Declaration of Independence get signed?",
        option1: "1971",
        option2: "1792",
        option3: "1776",
        option4: "1783",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "In what year did the U.S. enter World War I?",
        option1: "1905",
        option2: "1910",
        option3: "1917",
        option4: "1967",
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "The United States brought Alaska from which country?",
        option1: "Canada",
        option2: "United Kingdom",
        option3: "China",
        option4: "Russia",
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "The French and Indian war was also known as what?",
        option1: "The War of 1754",
        option2: "The Seven Years War",
        option3: "The bloody battle",
        option4: "The war of doom",
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Who won the battle of Bunker Hill?",
        option1: "The British",
        option2: "The English",
        option3: "The Americans",
        option4: "The French",
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What was the bloodiest single-day battle in U.S. history??",
        option1: "Battle of Gettysburg",
        option2: "Battle of Antietam",
        option3: "Battle of Waterloo",
        option4: "Battle of New Orleans",
        ans: 2
    }
]